# Jaber Rammal-CV

Srks662@gmail.com

0527723014

linkedin.com/in/jaber-rammal-584804214

github.com/jaber114

### Summary

Practical Software Engineer, Ability to Learn Quickly. Ability to Work individually or in a team.

Passionate employee with massive tech experience and knowledge. Have an excellent interpersonal skills, so for high sense of service and ability to handle several tasks.

### Education

## **Practical Software Engineer**

Ort Braude College, Karmiel

10/2019 - 10/2021,

**GPA OF 89** 

#### **Work Experience**

## Site Releability Engineer

K2view

05/2022 - 06/2022,

Ginosar,il

Constant Monitoring of customers production system(Linux and Windows os).

Creating monitoring dashboards and setting thresholds for tracking overall system health view using Grafana dashboard.

Measuring and optimizing production system performance.

Full control in Linux OS

## **Volunteer Experience**

Perach Program (10/2020 - 08/2021)

Tutor to Pupil in Elementary school.

## **Military Service**

Israel Givaty Unit (11/2015 - 07/2018)

Served the IDF for a full service as a warrior soldier at the givaty unit.

### Skills



Basic knowledge in(Kafka, Cassandra, automation, Reactjs).

### Personal Projects

#### MineSwepper(Java)

Minesweeper is a single-player puzzle video game. The objective of the game is to clear a rectangular board containing hidden "mines" or bombs without detonating any of them, with help from clues about the number of neighboring mines in each field. The game originates from the 1960s, and has been written for many computing platforms in use today. It has many variations and offshoots.

#### Old Scroll(Php,JavaScript,Html,Css,Mysql)

 Old Scroll is an Online Book Store that offers A regular Books With Shipping And Digital Books that Can Be Downloaded As a Pdf File.
Final Project with GPA of 85.

#### Who Want to Be A Millionare(Python)

This is a program, written in Python, that allows you to play 'Who Wants to be a Millionaire' in your command line! The game comes with all the bells and whistles you'd expect from the real thing. Including the three lifelines: 50/50Phone a Friend

#### Italy (Html, Css, JavaScript)

 This Project Includes A Popular Sites In Italy And the Most Famous Food in Italy

#### Books(Html,Css,Angular,Node js,MongoDB,Type Script)

 A Full Stack Online Books Store web that offers regular books to sell.

## Languages



## **Tools**

